questmindshare.com 2017-05-24

# Quest Mindshare Privacy Policy

## Your Privacy

QuestMindshare is committed to respecting the privacy of survey respondents and other online users of QuestMindshare's services. QuestMindshare's Privacy Policy governs the collection, use, retention and security of information gathered from survey respondents and other online users of QuestMindshare's services. QuestMindshare does not disclose any personally identifiable information about survey respondents to third parties, except in reporting the survey responses to QuestMindshare's clients or as required by law or legal process. Personally identifiable information means information that individually identifies you, such as your name, address, or email address. 

## Collected Information

QuestMindshare collects a wide range of information about survey respondents depending on the information needs of our surveys. For example, survey respondents may be requested to provide certain personally identifiable, financial or demographic information, as well as specific opinions about a variety of goods and services. Responses to all survey questions are completely voluntary. A survey respondent should only provide responses to questions they are comfortable answering and survey respondents may decline to answer any survey question. QuestMindshare reserves the right to report information gathered through the survey (demographic data, preferences, etc.) to QuestMindshare's clients. Any information you voluntarily disclose in the survey may be provided to the commissioner of the survey. QuestMindshare does not disclose a survey respondent's personally identifiable information to any clients or third parties other than the commissioner of the survey. 

## Additional Information From Survey Respondents

QuestMindshare's servers automatically recognize a survey respondent's domain name and IP addresses. No personal information about a survey respondent is revealed in this process. QuestMindshare may also gather anonymous "traffic data" that does not personally identify a survey respondent, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services QuestMindshare offers. QuestMindshare may use cookies on our platform to help us provide panelists with a better experience and to provide quality control and validation functions. No personal information is stored on any cookie that QuestMindshare uses. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at our website may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended. 

## Opt-Out

QuestMindshare honors respondents' requests to be excluded from marketing solicitations. To be removed from this mailing list, simply email your request to info@questmindshare.com. 

## Protecting Respondent Information

QuestMindshare is committed to handling the personal information and data of survey respondents with care and integrity. QuestMindshare uses industry standard security practices to protect such information and data. However, regardless of the security protections and precautions QuestMindshare undertakes, there is always a risk that personal data may be viewed and used by unauthorized third parties as a result of collecting and transmitting your data through the Internet. 

## Disputes Concerning Privacy Policy

If you have any complaint concerning how QuestMindshare has handled your personal information, please contact QuestMindshare immediately and QuestMindshare will make every reasonable effort to address and resolve your concerns. 

## Compliance

By signing up to and participating in the QuestMindshare panel, you agree to QuestMindshare's privacy policy and terms of use. 

## Contact Information

If you have questions about QuestMindshare's Privacy Policy, QuestMindshare 's practices related to the handling of data from survey respondents, or if you would like to have QuestMindshare remove your information from our database, please feel free to contact QuestMindshare at: 

QuestMindshare  
1 Yonge Street, Suite 1801  
Toronto, ON M5E 1W7  
Canada  
E-mail: [info@QuestMindshare.com](mailto:info@QuestMindshare.com)
